In this clip I want to talk to you about when to scrub your skin.
People often ask me do I scrub my skin in the morning?
Do I scrub my skin at night?
I like to do it at night because you really have the time to dedicate to your skin.
In the morning, everyone?s getting ready for work.
They don't have time.
They're rushing.
In the night time, you really have time to focus and give yourself a thorough massage and really get those dead skin cells off.
Also, throughout the day, especially living in a city, you have an accumulation of dead skin cells and dirt on your skin so we want to make sure that you remove that in the evening before you go to bed and scrubbing is really a great way to do so as opposed to just using a cleanser.
So definitely I want to reiterate nighttime and you're going to want to scrub depending on your skin type, one to seven times a week.
Again, for oily skin you can go four to seven times a week.
For mature skin, every day with a gentle scrub.
For sensitive skin, you want to do it like once, two times a week.